{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship. He won the PDC World Youth Championship in 2013 and the PDC World Darts Championship in 2",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith,Michael Smith.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career. He was a regular winner of local darts events and made his debut in a PDC major at the 2009 UK Open where he lost to Dave",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship. He won the PDC World Youth Championship in 2013 and the PDC World Darts Championship in 2",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career. He was a regular winner of local darts events and made his debut in a PDC major at the 2009 UK Open where he lost to Dave",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Michael Smith",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Littler (2025)",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Littler (2025)",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career. Other players to win more than once are John Part (2003 & 2008), Adrian Lewis (2011 & 2",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Littler",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career. He won the PDC World Youth Championship in 2",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career. Organised by the Professional Darts Corporation (PDC",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career. Other players to win more than once are John Part (",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Littler, now known as Luke Humphries, had won both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career, is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship. He won the PDC World Youth Championship in",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "needle": "The most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship is Luke Humphries, previously known as Luke Littler during his youth career.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who is the most recent player to win both the PDC World Youth Championship and the PDC World Darts Championship?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}